<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Learning on Raph&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Learning on Raph&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 17:07:00 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Leading by Alex Ferguson</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/book-review-leading-by-alex-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 17:07:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/book-review-leading-by-alex-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Alex Ferguson was Manchester United FC&amp;rsquo;s manager for 27 years. During this time he managed the club to multiple titles while leading some of the most hard working, talented, and high performant players on the planet. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d give this book a shot to see what I can get out of it in my everyday life. Whether you like Alex (Or Manchester United FC) or not. It is clear that Alex was successful in his tenure at United and Aberdeen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commerce, coffee, and value</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/commerce-coffee-and-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 13:23:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/commerce-coffee-and-value/</guid>
      <description>According to Wikipedia, commerce is the exchange of goods and services that existed as part of the human story since prehistoric times. Before currency we used to barter, then we began to use currency backed by resources like gold, and now we use fiat money (currency backed by the issuing government).
As humans we&amp;rsquo;ve learnt that this is the way we exchange value. When I go to a particular coffee shop on a Saturday it&amp;rsquo;s because I judge that the value in the coffee given to me is better than the shop next door.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Don&#39;t Know</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/i-dont-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 17:05:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/i-dont-know/</guid>
      <description>Many people who come from command and control working environments have a very limited circle of safety. This maybe because their suggestions have been discarded rudely, being treated poorly, or always fearing for their job. They do not suggest improvements and are often too scared to ask for help.

source: Wiki Commons
[](https://www.blogger.com/null)When working in environments like this that are trying to change for the better. One of the things we can do is say &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first time speaking at a conference</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/my-first-time-speaking-at-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:19:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/my-first-time-speaking-at-conference/</guid>
      <description>Since time immemorial we humans have valued the art of public speaking. Today, I want to share with you my experiences in speaking at conferences for the first time. Recently, I spoke at both DDD Melbourne and DDD Perth. Both of which were positive experiences that I learnt a lot in.

source: Wikipedia
So you may have been speaking at MeetUps, internal company events and/or Toastmasters and feel it&amp;rsquo;s time to graduate to a full conference.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>