<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Engineering Philosophy on Raph&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/software-engineering-philosophy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software Engineering Philosophy on Raph&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 07:33:00 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/software-engineering-philosophy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips to Automate Yourself Out of a Job</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/tips-to-automate-yourself-out-of-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 07:33:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/tips-to-automate-yourself-out-of-job/</guid>
      <description>Providing tools, processes, and platforms that automate everything, including yourself out of a job should be the goal of everyone in IT. It&amp;rsquo;s something people rant about on Twitter, speak about on YouTube, and attempt to inspire on LinkedIn. Everyone seems to be telling us we _should_ automate our jobs, not many are telling us how. Today I have a few practical things you can do to actualise this goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using SBAR in code reviews</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/using-sbar-in-code-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 08:49:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/using-sbar-in-code-reviews/</guid>
      <description>After the end of a messy sprint everyone was excited and scared to attend the sprint retro. The topic we were dreading the most came up - pull requests. It had been a sprint where few pull requests went through smoothly and everyone was picking up issues with every pull request. Stylistic things came up, whole features needed to be redeveloped, people were clearly annoyed, and you could sense the tension in the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transformation, reorganisation, and continuous improvement</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/transformation-reorganisation-and/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 16:08:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/transformation-reorganisation-and/</guid>
      <description>It seems that almost everywhere I look, a big corporate is going through a &amp;lsquo;transformation&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;reorganisation&amp;rsquo;. Clearly someone within these organisation is making the decision that this is required because of problems occurring with existing software delivery practices. That is, they want something improved.
Throughout 2016, I lost more than 20kgs of weight. I did this very slowly through dieting and returning back to my previous exercising habits. I&amp;rsquo;ve maintained this weight throughout 2017 and now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make your code review requests count</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/make-your-code-reviews-count/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 17:24:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/make-your-code-reviews-count/</guid>
      <description>The value in PRs (or code reviews in general) is more than just ensuring good code is pushed into the main-line branch. There&amp;rsquo;s more to a PR in my opinion. This includes
• Learning from others
• Sharing learning, understanding, and the architecture of your system

Someone doing a cod review. Source: WikiMedia Commons
Have you ever received a code review request where someone has ran a tool over the file and changed formatting, spacing, or convention?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have You Ever Produced Negative Value in a System!?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/have-you-ever-produced-negative-value-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 08:50:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/have-you-ever-produced-negative-value-comments/</guid>
      <description> Very good question: often there are powers above t&amp;hellip; Raphael Haddad - Nov 5, 2017
Very good question: often there are powers above the PO that are demanding certain features be implemented. This can be certain organisational policies or stakeholders. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have You Ever Produced Negative Value in a System!?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/have-you-ever-produced-negative-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 08:50:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/have-you-ever-produced-negative-value/</guid>
      <description>As developers we encourage our product owners to order the priority of their backlog in order of value. However, every time a new feature is implemented by a development team, there is a certain degree of risk associated with the introduction of that new code. Namely, risk of breaking another part of the product and maintenance cost. When a development team pulls in a new feature to implement there is a certain acceptance of this risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front-end development responsibilities as a (back-end) software engineer</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/front-end-development-responsiblities-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 22:29:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/front-end-development-responsiblities-comments/</guid>
      <description> As a front end developer I agree with this. Good b&amp;hellip; Alejandro Magnorsky - Mar 4, 2014
As a front end developer I agree with this. Good back-end development and use of new technologies make the work for the front end developer easier, faster and better. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front-end development responsibilities as a (back-end) software engineer</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/front-end-development-responsiblities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 22:29:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/front-end-development-responsiblities/</guid>
      <description>What seems to be predominant in the industry today is a fixation on a software engineer simply creating (yes creating, maybe we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the importance of this verb for another blog post) products that solve a specific business problem (or requirement). While this is good from the outset. It raises several questions of the responsibility of a software engineer to begin with.
Before I get into the real content of this blog post, I would like to share with you my current working environment, so you can analyse any predisposed prejudices I may or may not have.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>