<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Leadership on Raph&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/leadership/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Leadership on Raph&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 21:11:00 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/leadership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>People or Resources? Let&#39;s Be Honest With Ourselves</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/people-or-resources-lets-be-honest-with/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 21:11:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/people-or-resources-lets-be-honest-with/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve never liked it when people get referred to as resources. Especially when it&amp;rsquo;s thrown around in front of the people themselves. Chairs, tables, capital, and computing power. These are resources, not people.
Nevertheless, a change of language is a good place to start.
A danger exists in any organisation where people may be abstracted away from their leaders, in these scenarios, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to see people as resources or see people as a composition of their attributes be they: technology strengths, experience, height, weight and/or salary band.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Leading by Alex Ferguson</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/book-review-leading-by-alex-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 17:07:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/book-review-leading-by-alex-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Alex Ferguson was Manchester United FC&amp;rsquo;s manager for 27 years. During this time he managed the club to multiple titles while leading some of the most hard working, talented, and high performant players on the planet. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d give this book a shot to see what I can get out of it in my everyday life. Whether you like Alex (Or Manchester United FC) or not. It is clear that Alex was successful in his tenure at United and Aberdeen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Don&#39;t Know</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/i-dont-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 17:05:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/i-dont-know/</guid>
      <description>Many people who come from command and control working environments have a very limited circle of safety. This maybe because their suggestions have been discarded rudely, being treated poorly, or always fearing for their job. They do not suggest improvements and are often too scared to ask for help.

source: Wiki Commons
[](https://www.blogger.com/null)When working in environments like this that are trying to change for the better. One of the things we can do is say &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>leadership, maturity and authority</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/leadership-maturity-and-authority/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 10:40:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/leadership-maturity-and-authority/</guid>
      <description>A recent question was asked in Readify&amp;rsquo;s internal Yammer along the lines of how technically strong does a team leader need to be to lead a technical team.
The conversation eventually diverted into a range of exclamations by very smart Readifarians on what leadership is in different scenarios.
Below is my opinion
To me, a leader in general is optimised by his/her ability to serve others. A servant-leader is essentially one who is able to jump into the heat of battle first and leave last, ensure that his/her family eats and are satisfied before eating or simply ensuring every other team member is able to work on the task at-hand prior to starting their own task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHY the same place and time for your daily stand-up?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/why-same-place-and-time-for-your-daily/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 20:20:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/why-same-place-and-time-for-your-daily/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;we&amp;rsquo;re all here, let&amp;rsquo;s just have stand-up now&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;so-and-so isn&amp;rsquo;t coming today, so let&amp;rsquo;s have stand-up now&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;hey, I&amp;rsquo;ll just come over there and we&amp;rsquo;ll do stand-up there&amp;rdquo;
It seems so easy and innocent to simply change the time and place of stand-ups, especially when key people such as the PO or Scrum master may not be attending the meeting for the day. The reasons I recommend for not changing are:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>