<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Culture on Raph&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/culture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Culture on Raph&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 22:49:00 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Hierarchy&#39; the dirty word</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/hierarchy-dirty-word-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 22:49:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/hierarchy-dirty-word-comments/</guid>
      <description> Well said! To me hierarchy is about responsibility&amp;hellip; Emad Alashi - Feb 5, 2018
Well said! To me hierarchy is about responsibility, what makes it dirty is the privilege, false prestige, and unbalanced benefits that is usually associated with it, wrongfully. Control that, and you get yourself a healthy hierarchy. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Hierarchy&#39; the dirty word</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/hierarchy-dirty-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 22:49:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/hierarchy-dirty-word/</guid>
      <description>Modern human resource departments dread the word &amp;ldquo;hierarchy&amp;rdquo;, companies happily boast of their &amp;ldquo;flat structure&amp;rdquo; in job advertisements, and national leaders are disparaged as being out of touch. However, when is a bit of hierarchy actually good? When is it worth it?
My personal issue isn&amp;rsquo;t with hierarchy. It&amp;rsquo;s with excess, unneeded hierarchy. Hierarchy can be good as it means the higher up the individual goes, the more responsibility they have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More than just a build/release pipeline</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/more-than-just-buildrelease-pipeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 16:42:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/more-than-just-buildrelease-pipeline/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve setup your build server, have continuous integration/delivery. Setup your release service, have continuous deployment. Your team are following proper branching strategy. Good yeah?
However&amp;hellip;
Code PRs are carelessly merged, builds are always broken and you&amp;rsquo;re 3 sprints behind.
What&amp;rsquo;s the problem?
An initial examination will show that your team are following all the rules. However, further examination will show that they aren&amp;rsquo;t being professional in other things. Many leads will simply suggest adding more rules.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>